Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Favorite Green Grass Cake
Episode 34
The annual Flower Baby selection event is about to begin.
We welcome all the Flower Mentors and Mud Mentors here today.
As always, the Flower Babies will take the stage to show off their talents.
If a Flower Mentor or Mud Mentor sees a Flower Baby they like,
remember to press the selection button.
So, all I have to do is press a button? That sounds pretty simple.
Alright, let’s invite the first Flower Baby to the stage.
Hello, everyone. My name is Jiajia.
My talent is dancing.
Jiajia’s dance moves are incredibly dynamic and exceptionally elegant.
I believe she can awaken the Dazzling Dance Flower Spark and become a dancer flower.
So, are the mentors who wish to choose Jiajia ready?
Begin.
Friendly reminder:
The more times you press the button, the brighter the lantern shines.
Within the allotted time,
only the mentor with the brightest lantern gets to choose the Flower Baby.
Why didn’t you say so earlier?
Congratulations.
Congratulations to Kui Huahua for choosing Jiajia.
What’s up with these flowers? They are so fast!
No worries, we still have plenty of amazing Flower Babies.
Let’s welcome the next one.
—An all-around math genius, —I want!
—Shushu. —I want, I want!
The little skateboarding prince, A Fei.
The boxing kid,
Xiao Gui.
I want, I want, I want!
I couldn’t snag a single one.
So, let’s welcome the next one.
Hello everyone, my name is Zhuangzhuang.
This Flower Baby is powerfully built; he might awaken the Giant Strength Sunflower Spark in the future.
He might even awaken the Light Cotton Spark, just like Xi Huahua.
Light Cotton is the strongest Spark in our tribe.
That means
he could become an outstanding flower, just like Xi Huahua.
So Xi Huahua is actually that amazing?
It’s a shame that only Xi Huahua and the other one can have him right now.
I’m definitely going to pick this Flower Baby this time.
In your dreams.
Take your positions.
Begin.
Congratulations, Mei Huahua.
With him, I’ll definitely be the first to enter the Trial Grounds and get the fragment.
I’m the only one left without one.
Xi Huahua, don’t lose heart. We still have one final, special Flower Baby.
What? There’s still a special one?
It’s him.
I finally have a Flower Baby!
Elder.
Today’s Flower Baby selection has concluded successfully.
Let’s go.
What’s wrong with everyone?
He looks just like Paddi.
I’ll go first! I’ll go first!
I have a question.
Hold on, one at a time.
You go first.
Paddi, I’m in trouble…
I’ve gained weight. What should I do?
Then you have to fight fire with fire.
I suddenly don’t want to lose weight anymore. Let’s dig in together.
With the right mindset, everything falls into place.
Next.
I was trying to cook by the river today and discovered my rice cooker wouldn’t work.
Paddi, what should I do?
Then you probably need this:
A self-charging rice cooker.
Right, there’s no electricity by the river.
How could I use a rice cooker?
Paddi, you’re so smart.
I never thought being the village chief would be so easy.
I have a question.
What if that monster comes to Goats’ Village again to steal the fragment?
What do you think we should do?
Well…
What is a mentor supposed to do?
I never expected Xi Huahua to become Lan Baobao’s mentor.
That Lan Baobao is notorious for being the laziest Flower Baby of all.
Gluttonous, lazy, and disobedient.
He’s already driven away many mentors.
Whoever teaches him is out of luck.
But Xi Huahua is also our best mentor.
I’ve been looking at his “Flower Notes”.
The teaching plan outlined in there is excellent.
As expected of Xi Huahua.
That notes you were just talking about…
Could I have a look at it?
The Flower Mentor and the Flower Baby must complete a trial mission.
First, they must establish a relationship of trust between mentor and student.
A relationship of trust?
Time to wake up, Lan Baobao.
Hurry up and wake up.
Sleeping so soundly—just like Paddi.
If he’s like Paddi, maybe there’s a way.
If Weslie is here, What would he do?
Right, I need to think like Weslie.
Fast asleep.
I’ve got an idea.
Who knew sleeping was actually my way of thinking?
So is this the method Paddi mentioned?
I don’t know; let’s just trust Paddi.
I’m back.
Why are there so many mushrooms?
Paddi, it’s not mushroom season right now.
I’m not gathering them to eat.
They serve a very important purpose.
This is the Spicy Mushroom; it tastes numbing and hot.
This is the Bouncy Mushroom; it has a super springy texture.
This is the Hug Mushroom; its cap is huge and delicious.
But everything you’ve described is just about their texture.
Now, Paddi is the only one left guarding the fragment in Green Green Grassland.
Looks like I’ve won this time.
We won’t let you get away with it.
Even though Paddi is usually lazy, gluttonous,
slapdash, and timid,
he is absolutely trustworthy when it counts.
That’s hard to believe.
Just wait and see.
Alright then.
The monsters are coming!
Don’t panic, everyone; have faith in my mushroom formation.
What’s happening? I’ve never seen a trap like this before.
Paddi, you’re amazing!
I knew you could do it.
It worked!
Paddi, you’re amazing.
I had no idea these mushrooms were so powerful.
Paddi, how did you discover them?
Let’s not talk about the past.
I can’t tell them I tried them all out.
We won a great victory; let’s celebrate together,
and have some delicious grass cake!
Will do.
Let me prepare it.
Where is the Mentor? Did he get angry and leave too?
Must be.
He only knows how to sleep; how could he possibly become a flower?
There are flowers that love to sing. There are flowers that love to dance.
There are flowers that love to paint. And naturally, there are also flowers that love to sleep.
Lan Baobao, I made a grass cake that you’ve never tasted before.
It smells so good.
It’s delicious.
This creamy grass cake fills me with energy.
I feel so happy.
It worked.
Oh no, keeping my wings out like this
uses up too much energy.
Here, you look really hungry.
Let’s eat together.
Thank you.
Does the fact that you’re willing to share the cake with me
mean that we’ve established a bond of trust?
Do you know why I shared the cake with you?
Wasn’t it because of the cake?
There are flowers that love to sing.
There are flowers that love to dance.
There are flowers that love to paint.
And naturally, there are also flowers that love to sleep.
No one has ever spoken well of me before, so…
So, we’ve established a bond of trust?
You’ve passed my first test.
The first test?
It all depends on how you perform in the next test.
You need to give it your all
Who’s the mentor now?
I’m going to dig in
Dig in
Paddi, what’s wrong?
Did we not make the cake well?
I…
Paddi, the cake you made is amazing
I hope we can always be happy together
No, it’s just…I was thinking about Sparky and the others
I wonder how they’re doing over there.
That’s easy; we can just communicate via the drones following them.
Why is the signal gone?
What?
There are two more intruders.
Retract.
Their mission is to rescue Mr. Slowy, and mine is to stop you.
Overestimating yourself.
So? Is there a signal yet?
The drones are likely destroyed; I can’t see the playback.
I don’t know if they’ve run into any danger.
I want to go help them.
But…
You go ahead; we’ve got things covered here.
With the mushroom formation you set up, we’ll definitely be fine.
You guys…
Don’t worry.
We are also Mighty Little Defenders.
I’ll leave this place in your hands.
Everyone, wait for me.
To be continued